[{
    "theme": "ðŸ©º Pedir ayuda en la farmacia",
    "langread": "en",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "My friend doesnâ€™t feel well.",
            "answers": ["mi amiga no se siente bien"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I donâ€™t feel well.",
            "answers": ["no me siento bien"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Whatâ€™s the problem?",
            "answers": ["Â¿CuÃ¡l es el problema?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Nausea (feminine form).",
            "answers": ["mareada"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Nausea (masculine form).",
            "answers": ["mareado"]
        },
        {
            "question": "You look pale.",
            "answers": ["estÃ¡s pÃ¡lido"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Your face is red.",
            "answers": ["la cara estÃ¡ roja"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I already see.",
            "answers": ["ya veo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "My throat hurts too.",
            "answers": ["me duele la garganta tambiÃ©n"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many days?",
            "answers": ["Â¿cuÃ¡ntos dÃ­as?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you eat something different?",
            "answers": ["Â¿comiste algo diferente?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "More than usual?",
            "answers": ["Â¿mÃ¡s de lo normal?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Is it the first time?",
            "answers": ["Â¿es la primera vez?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Octopus.",
            "answers": ["pulpo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't know if it comes from that.",
            "answers": ["no sÃ© si viene de eso"]
        },
        {
            "question": "A reaction.",
            "answers": ["una reacciÃ³n"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you take the sun?",
            "answers": ["Â¿tomaste el sol?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you pregnant?",
            "answers": ["Â¿estÃ¡s embarazada?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Itâ€™s nothing serious.",
            "answers": ["no es nada grave"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I'll give you these medicines.",
            "answers": ["le doy estos medicamentos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Since two weeks ago.",
            "answers": ["desde hace dos semanas"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Iâ€™ve been speaking with Miguel for one hour.",
            "answers": ["hablo con Miguel desde hace una hora"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Iâ€™ve been eating octopus for ten years.",
            "answers": ["como el pulpo desde hace diez aÃ±os"]
        }
    ]
}]
